权欲 前情回顾
Previously on Power...
比沃拉・鲁伊斯喜好毒蛇
Vibora Ruiz has a thing for poisonous snakes.
我有办法
I got you just the ticket to get you
让你进入索尔达多的高级委员会
in the high council of the Soldado Nation.
赎罪日快乐 比沃拉
Happy high holy day, Vibora.
我丈夫和汤米之间有什么秘密?
What's going on between my husband and Tommy?
你来告诉我
You can tell me.
这会是我们之间的另一个小秘密
It'll be another one of our little secrets.
我想知道我们究竟在做什么
I want to know what we're doing here.
单纯的激情释放?
Are we just fucking?
我正在为你作抉择
I am making a choice with you.
她可不是那种谁都可以上的公交车
This ain't some skank-ass broad.
霍莉不一样 她很特别
Holly's different. She's special.
但愿你没有对她透露我们其他的事
You better not have told her about our other thing.
我早说过一直就是鲁伊斯从中作鬼
I told you it was Ruiz all along.
是是 除了你说那是阿尼巴尔干的
Yeah, except when you said it was Anibal.
除了那时候 我无所谓
Except then. I don't care.
我现在只想杀了那个混账东西
Now I just want to kill a motherfucker.
鲁伊斯被捅了
Ruiz got stabbed.
下手的不是我们雇的牙买加人
It wasn't the Jamaicans we hired.
有人在追踪他 失了手
Someone went after him and missed.
他没死
He ain't dead.
那时候 卡南管教着我们
Back then, Kanan kept us in line,
教我们如何行事 锻炼我们成为汉子
taught us the business, made us men.
我和幽灵欠你父亲很多
Ghost and I owe your father big.
所以你在这里
That's why you're here.
将
Check.
这次你拿我没辙了 卡南
You ain't gonna get me this time, K.
我一直在练习
I've been practicing.
看得出来
Yes, you have.
将军 混账
Checkmate, motherfucker.
你在胡说什么?
What the fuck you talking about?
你自己看到了
You see it.
别让我在嘲笑你了 狗家伙
Don't make me smile you up right here, motherfucker.
你妈妈不会喜欢掀开了的棺材
Your mama won't appreciate no closed casket.
卡南 有人来看你
Kanan, you got a visitor.
是吗?
Yeah?
别再满口胡言地说什么西班牙开局
You need to stop with that Ruy Lopez bullshit.
把棋子收拾好
Rack 'em back up.
我还会回来的
I'll be back.
我总是说同样的话
I been saying the same shit all along.
我们称之为起诉不当
We're calling it prosecutorial misconduct.
我才不管你们怎么叫
I don't give a fuck what you call it,
能让我出去就行
as long as it means I get out.
那个制止你的警官
The police officer that stopped you
承认起诉人不让他念
admitted that the prosecutor told him to omit
他的报告中特定段落
certain elements from his report,
包括他为何一上去就阻止你
including the fact that your back headlight,
说你的后灯
the reason why he stopped you in the first place,
不是爆了 而是被拆了...
wasn't blown out, but rather, had been removed...
- 嗯哼 - 灯泡被拧下来
- Mm-hmm. - The bulb unscrewed.
车箱里装着毒品
Somebody wanted me to get pulled over
有人还想让我靠边停车
with drugs in the trunk.
我这么跟我第一个律师说的
I told my first lawyer that shit.
他们陷害我
They set my ass up.
陷害你不要紧
It doesn't matter that you were set up.
重要的是起诉人有物证
It matters that the prosecutor had material evidence
可以验证他的说法 隐藏真相
to support that theory and hid those facts,
- 陪审团不会知情 - 好吧
- so the jury never knew. - Okay.
检察官觉得
The D.A. figured,
卡南年纪轻轻的 还是个黑人 就认为他有罪
Kanan's young and black, he's guilty.
谁在乎所谓法律?
Who gives a shit about the rules?
这个检察官手下复查的案子
This D.A. has a bunch of cases
多了去了
under judicial review.
所以你得早点出来
That's why you're getting out fast.
什么时候?
When?
你穿成那样不冷吗?
Ain't you cold in that shit?
好几年都没有站在街角了
Stopped standing on the corner years ago.
在里面干活不用穿的圆鼓鼓的
Don't need no puffy working from the inside.
你也能干的 孩子 你很聪明
You could do it too, boy. You're smart.
不要了 我还是喜欢街道
No, man. I love the streets.
我并不想做个无家可归的人
I ain't trying to be no house nigga.
变化是由内而外的 罗拉
Change come from inside the house, Rolla.
哪个疯子想要改变啊?
Who the fuck want to change?
我听说鲁伊斯被袭击了
I heard Ruiz got hit.
在一个该死的脱衣舞俱乐部里被人捅了
Stabbed inside a motherfucking strip club.
妈的
God damn.
那个俱乐部本该是个圣地啊 懂我的意思吗?
Strip club supposed to be sacred, you feel me?
上一刻你还欲火焚身
One minute you getting a good dick burn,
下一秒就被人开肠破肚了
next, you getting gutted open like a fish.
嗯
Yeah.
街头巷尾传言是你干的
Streets are saying you did it.
你想听天气预报
You ask for the weather report,
他们说要下雨 你可别恼
don't get mad when they say it's gonna rain.
你觉得耳听为实?
You believe what you heard?
如果你在幕后操作
If y'all was behind it,
我们就该在鲁伊斯的葬礼上了
we'd be at Ruiz's funeral
此时此刻
right now.
不过先是阿尼巴尔 现在又搞这个?
But first Anibal, now this?
别怪黑人闲言碎语多
You can't blame niggas for wagging tongues.
貌似你要清理门户
Looks like you cleaning house.
要不你来消除竞争
Or you eliminating the competition.
来一口吗 阿姆?
'Sup, Em?
告诉过你别那么叫我
I told you to stop it with that shit.
我要是艾米纳姆 现在就会有女服务员
If I was Eminem, I would be getting
舔我的老二了
my dick sucked by some actress right now,
才不会跟你在外边 把蛋蛋冻掉
not freezing my balls off out here with you.
喂 罗拉说人们传言
Yo, Rolla says folks are saying
我们袭击了鲁伊斯
we called the hit on Ruiz.
真是胡说八道
That's some bullshit.
我们明天过去一趟
I say we go by tomorrow
让他明白我们的立场
and make sure he knows where we stand.
没人保护我可不进去
I wouldn't walk in unprotected.
索尔达多人可都是先行后闻
Soldados shoot first, ask questions after the fact.
要一起来吗 罗拉?
You want to come with me, Rolla?
你先进去
I'll let you go in first.
- 见到你真好 幽灵 - 好伙计
- Good to see you, G. - My man.
晚安 马歇尔
Night, Marshall.
操
Fuck you.
我一直不理解你为什么那么喜欢他
I never get why you like him so much.
他又忠诚又聪明
He's loyal, and he's smart.
他聪明过头 不知道我们的谋划
He's too smart to try some shit with Ruiz
是不会跟鲁伊斯掺合的
without knowing our play.
你觉得脱身有道能遮过去吗?
You think cool runnings gapped off?
遮什么?
Gapped off about what?
牙买加人为什么要对袭击未遂自吹自擂?
Why would the Jamaicans brag about a botched hit?
他们都没袭击鲁伊斯
They didn't even hit Ruiz.
还欠我们退料单
Owe us a motherfucking store credit.
我知道鲁伊斯没在真正的医院登记入住
I know Ruiz didn't check into no real hospital.
你要找出他的藏身之地
Make sure you know where he's hiding.
我们明天就去
We'll go there tomorrow.
罗拉有一件事说得对
Rolla is right about one thing.
如果索尔达多对我们起了疑心
If the Soldados suspect us,
就会手痒痒的想扣动扳机了
they'll have itchy trigger fingers.
我最好单独去
I better go alone.
绝对不行
No fucking way.
我不会让你在塔莎生日前夕
I ain't gonna let you get clipped
变成残废的
right before Tasha's birthday.
出了岔子 她永远不会原谅我
If the worst happens, she'll never forgive me.
你忘了她的生日?
You forgot about her birthday?
我去 兄弟 那可是你老婆
Damn, man, she's your wife.
怎么我记得 你却忘了?
How come I remember, you don't?
我要想的事太多了 汤米
I got a lot on my mind, Tommy.
好吧 不客气 我一出来就给你打电话
Well, you're welcome. I'll call you when I get out.
就这么做
Do that.
我们可以白天见的
We could've met you during the day.
这是不被他们发现
This is the only time I could get away
我还能跑掉的唯一时机
without them knowing I was gone.
这是实况播放 从现在开始
That's live, so from now on,
你们谈正事的时候
try to get yourself near Ruiz and his top guys
你要尽量靠近鲁伊斯和他的核心成员
when you're talking business.
特别是当他们提到洛沃斯或者经销商
Especially if they mention Lobos or the distributor.
我们要听到所有内容
We'll be able to hear everything.
所有的话 所以你干掉一个之前
Everything, so take your jacket off
记得把衣服脱掉
before you rub one out, okay?
我可不想听见那玩意儿
I don't want to hear that shit.
我以为你们才是卑鄙小人
I thought you were the reptile guy.
你应该是
You were supposed to.
鲁伊斯贴身保镖要在我身上找到这个
我就死定了
我们会一天二十四小时监控你
如果情况不妙 我们三十秒便可赶到
If anything happens, we'll be on you in 30 seconds.
扣动扳机用不了一秒
It takes less than a second for someone to pull the trigger.
那我们就晚了二十九秒
Then we'll be 29 seconds late.
妈的
Fuck this.
找个别的人当你们的告密者去
Get someone else to be your snitch.
诺克斯特工只是跟你开玩笑
Agent Knox is just fucking with you.
你不会有事的
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
- 我保证 - 你保证?
- You have my word. - Your word?
等我躺在血泊中 我回想起来的
I'll remember that when I'm bleeding out.
这么想吧
Look at it this way.
要么戴上麦克 要么在纽约州新新监狱碰运气
Either wear the mic, or try your luck up at sing sing.
我听说帕多斯在哪儿混得不错
Pedos do really good up there, I hear.
- 你真该死 - 你会跟他调情吗 诺马?
- Fuck you. - You flirting with him, Nomar?
够了!
Enough!
戴上麦克 我们会让你回来的
你别无选择
You don't have a choice.
你们全都去死吧
Fuck all of you then.
你今天回家早了
You're home early.
还以为你一整夜都会在俱乐部
Figured you'd be at the club all night.
不是在俱乐部 我跟汤米一起
Wasn't at the club. I was with Tommy.
我想问你汤米怎么了
I'd ask you what's up with Tommy,
但你是不会告诉我的 所以...
but you ain't gonna tell me anyway, so...
好吧 我不想你让你漂亮的脸蛋
Well, I don't want your pretty little head
为这件事皱起眉头
to worry about any of that.
我想让你专心地为自己
I want you to concentrate on throwing yourself
安排一场最盛大 最豪华的生日派对
the biggest, best birthday party money can buy.
我以为你忘了呢
I thought you forgot.
那现在呢?
Now, you see that?
看来你错了
You thought wrong.
对 好吧 要是你几周前这样和我说
Yeah, well, it would've been nice
那就好了
to know a couple of weeks ago.
但这就不叫惊喜了
But that would've ruined
不是吗?
the whole surprise now, wouldn't it?
这话听起来有点假
Sounds like bullshit to me.
听着 宝贝 我事先都计划好了
Look, baby, I had this whole thing planned.
我做了 然后 我想到
I did, and then I thought,
要安排你的生日派对 谁能比得上你自己?
well, who better to design your party than you?
不管怎样 你都会讨厌别人布置的派对
You'd hate what anyone else put together anyway.
这倒是
You got me there.
我已经通知了坎托斯
I already called Kantos.
你和拉凯莎明天过去
You and Lakeisha go down tomorrow,
想要什么要什么 想邀请谁邀请谁
get whatever you want, invite whoever.
你丈夫我有你就满足了
Your husband's got you.
- 谢谢 宝贝 - 恩哼
- Thank you, baby. - Mm-hmm.
好吧 我保证不会让你倾家荡产的 好吗?
Okay, I promise I won't break the bank, okay?
不要做无法实现的承诺 女士
Don't make no promises you can't keep, woman.
- 我保证 - 好吧
- I promise. - Okay.
你睡不着吗?
You can't sleep?
有心事?
Something on your mind?
听着
Look.
我知道
I know.
听到自己的好友对另一位好友不忠
It sucks to hear your best friend
的确是件令人不快的事
is cheating on your other best friend.
那些低贱的女人总是想要勾引
Skanks throw themselves at club owners
俱乐部的拥有者
all the time.
他会清醒过来的
He'll come back to his senses.
随便他 我不管了
Whatever. I'm over that.
我很好
I'm fine.
只是有点工作上的事
It's just work stuff.
你什么时候回来?
What time are you gonna be home?
我在想
I was thinking
我该为你做点辛辛那提辣椒酱了
I'd make you some Cincinnati Chili.
你知道的 浇在意大利面上 和肉桂粉一起?
You know, over spaghetti, with cinnamon?
我打赌你从没吃过
I bet you never had that.
听起来好恶心
Sounds fucking disgusting.
你... 吃过之后会喜欢的
You... Are gonna eat it and like it.
听着 霍霍 我...
Look, Hol, I...
我今晚可能会晚点回来
I might be a little late tonight.
多晚?
How late?
我...
I...
你可以选另一个晚上给我做这些吃的
you can make that shit for me another night.
另一个晚上?
Another night?
你喜欢我在你身边 是吗?
You like having me around, huh?
是的 我喜欢
Yeah, I do.
不管怎样我今天都要去购物
I need to go shopping today anyway.
我要去看看你的厨房都有些什么吃的
I'll see what you got in the kitchen.
那儿什么都没有
There ain't shit in there.
这盒谷物两年前就过期了!
This box of cereal expired two years ago!
我告诉过你
Told ya.
汤米 这是什么?
Tommy, what's this?
现金
Cash.
才不是
No shit.
谢谢你富有理解力的解释
Thank you for that comprehensive explanation.
哪来的?
From where?
俱乐部
From the club.
这是胡扯!
Bullshit it is!
我不喜欢存银行 就这样
I don't like banks, that's all.
这有什么问题?
What's the problem?
厨房里还有四个
There are four more of those in the kitchen.
你就是个银行
You are a bank.
你能不能别随便窥探隐私
You shouldn't be fucking snooping.
去你的 汤米
Fuck you, Tommy.
我告诉过你别骗我
I told you not to fucking lie to me.
看看你这一身 混得不错嘛
Look at you, all G'ed up.
你发了?
You stacking?
什么? 不 不 不
What? Nah, nah, nah.
是幽灵叔叔帮我买的这身西装
Uncle G bought me this suit.
象征着尊敬
Sign of respect.
你一定在加快步伐
You must be stepping it up.
是的 也许等你一年内出狱的话
Yeah, and maybe when you get out in a year,
你懂的 也许我会有所成就的
you know, maybe I'll be somebody.
也许
Maybe.
嘿 我听说外面的混蛋在发牢骚
Hey, I hear motherfuckers out there beefing.
是索尔达多族 泰诺人吗?
Is it the Soldados, the Tainos?
- 嗯... - 放轻松
- Um... - It's okay.
这里说话很安全
It's safe to talk here.
- 泰诺人遭袭了 - 真的?
- The Tainos got hit. - Yeah?
是的 然后有人还把阿尼巴尔杀了
Yeah, and somebody took Anibal out too.
- 不会吧 - 没错 是的
- No shit. - Yeah, yeah.
然后鲁伊斯也被袭了
And Ruiz got hit.
可能是为了报复或者不是
Maybe in retribution or maybe not,
但是我不是很清楚
but I don't really know.
为什么你不知道
Why you don't know?
因为我不问不该问的
Cause I don't ask no questions.
你的幽灵叔叔把你提拔上来
Your Uncle G pulled you in,
所以他希望你问问题
so he expects you to ask questions.
他希望你也参与进来
He expects you to come to play, son.
我只是他的司机
I'm just his driver.
只要你这么看待自己
As long as you see yourself as that,
你就永远只是司机
it's all you'll ever be.
我们都是从小弟做起的 兄弟
We all start off small, man.
运毒的 贩毒的 收高利贷的
Runner, corner, cash-kid.
问题是 你怎么看待自己
Question is, what are you gonna make of yourself?
- 我努力工作 - 这很好
- I'm working hard. - That's good.
但是还不够
But not good enough.
你都不知道幽灵的下一个计划
How you supposed to learn how G thinks
又是怎么知道幽灵是怎么想的呢?
if you don't know his next move, hmm?
我不知道
I don't know.
我在告诉你
Yeah, I'm telling you.
幽灵在等待你去向他证明自己
G waiting on you to prove yourself.
证明给他你能接生意 参与其中
Show him you got the hustle. Get in there.
拿你该拿的
Take what's yours.
请告诉斯特恩先生 我打过电话要求安排会议
Please tell Mr. Stern that I called to set a meeting.
我打赌他忘了你的生日
I bet he did forget your birthday.
现在这是让他付出代价的时候了
Now it's your chance to make him pay.
让我们把男缸放在这儿
Let's put the man-quarium right here.
到底什么是男缸?
Girl, what the fuck is a man-quarium?
一个用来装男人的大鱼缸
A giant fish tank filled with men.
你失去理智了
You're out of your mind.
- 这是你的三十岁生日 - 的确
- It's your 30th birthday. - Exactly.
我希望派对既成熟又性感
And I want it to be grown and sexy,
而不是寒酸的要命
but not with no ghetto-ass shit.
圣・帕特里克夫人是对的
Mrs. St. Patrick's right.
我认为我们可以想点
I was thinking we can come up
能让派对充满惊喜的点子
with a birthday shout out at the top of every hour.
我们可以弄个签名鸡尾酒
We can come up with a signature cocktail
或者弄点气球或是撒撒五彩纸片
or maybe even do a balloon or a confetti drop.
首先
First of all,
她快要三十岁了 不是十三岁
she's turning 30, not 13.
所以别踩气球了 好吗?
So enough with the balloon stomping, all right?
然后确保有足够诗珞珂鸡尾酒
And make sure there's plenty of Ciroc,
因为这是我的客人要喝的
because that's all my people drink,
最后 别弄椰子 因为我对坚果过敏
and no coconut because I'm allergic to nuts.
谢谢啦
Thank you.
我真的等不及要见你
I really couldn't wait to see you.
- 我也是 - 我开始...
- Yeah. - I'm starting...
我开始在工作上分心
I'm starting to get distracted at work.
这不好
It's bad.
也有好的
Not all bad.
喂?
Hello?
好的 知道了
Yes, that's fine.
我马上过去
I'll be right there.
你还好吗?
You okay?
一切都好吗?
Everything good?
是我父亲
It's my father.
他 精神状况不太好
He's, uh, not well.
我得走了
I gotta go.
如果你愿意我可以付开房的钱
I can pay for the room if you want.
不 你开什么玩笑 当然我付房钱
No, are you kidding? I got the room.
别担心房钱
Don't worry about the room.
他在长岛
He's out in Long Island.
得乘火车去
Gotta get the train.
帕斯说他在那里过得不开心 我该听进去的
Paz said he was unhappy there, and I should've listened.
我都能听到他在里屋尖叫的声音了
I could hear him screaming in the back room.
嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
他会好起来的
He's gonna be okay.
看着我
Look at me.
他会好起来的 对吗?
He's gonna be okay, all right?
我的车就在楼下 我可以载你去
My ride's downstairs. I can take you.
我想载你去
I want to take you.
听我说
你不在听!
You're not listening!
他根本不是威廉姆斯先生
为什么这个男人在威廉姆斯先生的床上?
Why is that man in Mr. Williams' bed?
爸爸 爸爸
Papi, Papi.
威廉姆斯先生去世了
安吉拉!
Angela!
是我
我在这儿
他死了?
三个月前就过世了
这儿没事了 谢谢你们
We're good here. Thank you.
不知道他们给我用了什么
让我犯困
没关系 闭上眼
你在这里很安全
You're safe here.
- 但是他们给我吃了什么 - 嘘
医生在照顾呢 爸爸
The doctors are looking after you, Papi.
我们都是
We all are.
帕斯 一会就来了 好吗?
Paz will be by later, okay?
你很快就会没事的
我认识你
你叫什么?
那是我朋友 杰米・圣・帕特里克
That's my friend, Jamie St. Patrick.
他开车送我过来
He drove me here.
他是那个街头的混混?
The punk from the corner?
那个毒贩子?
The drug dealer?
我记得我告诉过你离这个小子远点儿
I thought I told you to stay away from that boy.
- 他不是什么好东西 - 爸爸 爸爸 嘘
- He's no good. - Pap... Papi, shh.
我想你 安吉拉
你什么时候才能好好的 从学校搬回家啊?
威廉姆斯先生会跟你一起回来吗?
睡吧
他终于睡着了
He's finally asleep.
都不敢相信这居然是同一个人
It's so hard to believe he's the same man
过去因为拼写而责问我
that grilled me on spelling,
因为我得了"B" 就把我打到地上
grounded me when I got a "B."
天呐 有时候他真是个混蛋
God, he could be an asshole sometimes,
但是现在他...
but now he's...
他又无助 又恐惧
He's helpless, so scared.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我失态了
I'm a mess.
安琪 我能帮你做什么吗?
Angie, is there anything I can do?
什么事都可以
你什么也帮不了我
I don't think so,
除非你能让这些统统消失
unless you can make this all go away.
我是霍莉
This is Holly.
很明显我有比接电话
Obviously I'm doing something
更重要的事情在忙
more important than taking your call,
请留言
so leave a message.
嘿  给我回电话
Hey, call me back.
如果我没接到....
If I don't answer...
算了
Nevermind.
打给我
Just call me.
- 鲁伊斯让我来的 - 好 好
- Ruiz is expecting me. - Yeah, yeah.
我后腰上有把枪
I've got a nine on my waist.
脚踝上也有一把
And one on my ankle.
等下
Hold up.
啊噢 我把那个给忘了
Oops, I must have forgot about that one.
你他妈是兰博啊?
Who the fuck is you, Rambo?
电影第一滴血男主角
我现在能去见你们老板了吧?
Can I go see your boss now?
来吧
Come on.
他是来见头儿的
He's here to see Jefe.
- 搜身了吗? - 搜了
- He clean? - Yeah.
好的
All right.
哟 哟 来人了
Yo. Yo, we got a visitor.
你看起来真狼狈
You look like shit.
我不能去正规医院
I can't go to a regular hospital.
乱七八糟的问题太多
Too many fucking questions to answer.
谢谢
Gracias.
我们能单独谈谈吗?
Can we talk alone?
他们已经搜了我的身
They already patted me down,
缴了我的枪
took my gat.
你能来真好 幽灵在哪?
Nice of you to visit. Where's Ghost?
她不让我干
She won't let me fuck her in the ass.
虽然她妹妹让
Her sister will, though.
我被捅过两次 比中枪还惨
I been stabbed twice. I'd rather get shot.
那不是我们干的 鲁伊斯
It wasn't us, Ruiz.
我听说的可不是这样
I heard different.
我们跟你没过节
We ain't got no beef with you.
你是毒贩子 你跟谁都有过节
You're drug dealers. You got beef with everybody.
他们也是这么说你的
They say the same thing about you.
没准是阿尼巴尔的人 罗拉也有可能
Maybe it was Anibal's people. Maybe it was Rolla.
这俩混蛋哪个都不喜欢你
Neither of those motherfuckers any love for you,
而且 难道真的就没有其他人想让你死吗?
and really, nobody else wants you dead?
你也是个毒贩子 鲁伊斯
You're a drug dealer too, Ruiz.
很多敌人你自己都不知道
You got more enemies than you even know.
听着
Look.
如果我和幽灵策划的这次袭击
If me and Ghost was behind this hit,
我现在就不会在这里
I wouldn't be here right now,
你也不会
and neither would you.
听着
谁守着电梯呢?
Who's watching the elevator?
不知道
头儿要人整天守着那儿
Jefe wants somebody there all day.
知道了
I got it.
快去
没问题
你能调清楚点吗?
Can you clean it up?
嗯 嗯 我不知道
Uh, uh, I don't know.
你都不知道幽灵派人袭击了我?
Would you even know if Ghost put out a hit on me?
你的伙伴最近的行为有些诡异
Your compai's been acting kind of strange lately,
很反常地对我特非常友好
going out of his way to be all nice to me,
但却在他自己安排的见面上不出现
but then not showing up at meetings he arranges.
虽然有这些破事
With all this bullshit going on,
他还是在避免引人注目
he's trying to keep a low profile,
这点你也应该做到
something you might want to consider doing.
庆祝这神圣的一天 有个婊子捅了我
Celebrating my high holy day, and this puta sticks me.
捅你的是个女孩?
The hitter was a girl?
她长什么样?
What'd she look like?
她看起来既甜美又阳光
She looked like ice cream and sunshine
直到她捅了我
till she stuck me.
豪乳 美臀
Great tits, beautiful ass,
拉丁女孩 健壮
Latin girl, strong.
袭击我们的也是她
A girl hit us too.
还能想起别的吗?
Anything else you remember?
我又没看她的脸
I wasn't looking at her face, man.
浅色卷发
Light hair, curly.
我们找到这个女孩 就知道是谁在袭击我们了
We find this girl, we find out who's been hitting us.
哦 你算说对了 鲁伊斯
Oh, you're goddamn right, Ruiz.
我们得一起找她
We in this together.
我离开这里之后就没再回来
I haven't been back here since I left.
当然 酒厂和宠物店
The Bodega got replaced, of course,
换地方了
with this pet store.
不过其他的
But otherwise
和以前都一样
just like the old days.
我觉得你该来杯奶昔
I thought you could use a milk shake.
嗯?
Hmm?
你觉得他们还做黑白配奶昔?
You think they still make black-and-whites?
所以我们才来这里
Well, that's why we here.
这是唯一能验证的方法 靓女
Only one way to find out, Miss Big-time.
噢
Oh.
稍等一下 宝贝
Just give me a second, baby.
怎么了?
What's up?
- 你在路上了吗? - 没 我吃午饭呢
- Are you on your way in? - No, I'm having lunch out
在林山
in Forest Hills.
你打电话就是为了听我的声音? 什么事?
You just want to hear my voice? What?
你老婆的生日...
Your wife's birthday...
你听起来挺严肃的 我在想办法把事情办好
you sounded serious, and I'm trying to make it work,
但是需要更多人手来加班
but I'm gonna have to call in more staff, pay overtime.
没问题
That's fine.
有个女的要二十箱伏特加
The other woman wanted 20 cases of Ciroc.
好吧 不管他们要什么 都满足 我得挂了
Yeah, whatever they need, just do it. I gotta go.
等下 还有件事 西蒙・斯特恩
Wait, there's one more thing. Simon Stern...
把事办成就行了
just make it happen.
你他妈干什么呢?
Fuck are you doing?
我得盯紧点万一他有事呢
Just staying close in case he needs something.
你们在玩女人的时候
I was the one who saved his life
可是我救了他的命
while you were all rubbing asses.
跟鲁伊斯在一起的家伙是谁?
Who's the blanquito in there with Ruiz?
那人是给我们供货的
That's the guy who gets us the products.
经销商
Distro.
我得进去
I'm going in.
哟 哟 哟 你会暴露我们的
Yo, yo, yo, yo. You'll blow our cover.
你要是想给女朋友打电话
You want to call your girlfriend and ask
问你能不能做这狗屁工作
if you can pretty please do your fucking job,
那你直接去打 行了吧?
you go for it, all right?
这案子我查了三年了
I've been on this case three years now.
如果洛沃斯的分销商在楼里的话
If Lobos' distributor's in that building,
我得去看看
I'm getting a look.
干他娘的
Son of a fucking bitch.
谁会认识那样一个女孩呢?
Who would know a girl like that?
阿尼巴尔死了
Anibal's dead,
罗拉不会用女人去搞暗杀
I don't think Rolla would use a female for wetwork.
- 洛沃斯 - 幽灵不这么觉得
- Lobos. - Ghost don't think so.
你 还有 幽灵...
You, Ghost...
转移注意力了
Have taken your eye off the ball.
没有
Nah, man.
我们在等待时机
We just waiting for our pitch.
现在我要去找到这个娘们
Now, I'm gonna find this bitch.
我得把事情摆平
I'm gonna make things righ with us.
我会找到那女孩的 别担心
I'ma find that girl. Don't you worry.
他要出去了
放轻松
那真是个疯子
Yo, that's one crazy motherfucker.
哟 哟 哟
Yo, yo, yo.
你找哪家?
十五C
我来看奶奶
楼下那层 哥们
One floor down, homey.
现在觉得好些没?
You feel better now?
好点了 不过只是奶昔的原因
A little, but only because of the milk shake.
我需要接个电话
I gotta take this.
接吧 我理解
Go ahead. I understand.
一切还好吗?
Everything cool?
我还活着 如果你问的是这个
I'm still alive, if that's what you mean.
- 很好 那就晚点再谈 - 不 现在就谈
- Good, let's talk later. - No, we need to talk now.
现在不方便 我要挂了
I can't talk right now. I gotta go.
现在你有我百分之百的注意力了
All right, you got my undivided attention.
操
Fuck.
您已拨通347-555...
You've reached 347-555...
坎托斯 我是汤米 你老板在哪?
Kantos, it's Tommy. Where's your boss?
是不是在和什么夜总会里的混蛋谈话?
Is he talking to some club asshole over there?
我以为他在林山
I thought he was having lunch with you
和你吃午饭
out in Forest Hills.
- 他在林山? - 他是这么说的
- He's in Forest Hills? - That's what he said.
很快挂了电话
Got off the phone in a hurry.
- 很抱歉我父亲说了那些 - 啊...
- I'm sorry my dad said that... - Ah.
说你是个混混 毒贩
About you being a punk, a drug dealer.
他只是在说他所记得的
Yeah, he remembers what he remembers.
他记错了
He remembers wrong.
好人不是想变就变的 杰米
You don't just become a good guy, Jamie.
你能有今天 是因为你过去就一直是好人
To get where you are now means you were always one inside.
关于你的事 我一直都是对的
I was right about you all along.
你总是带我出来吃东西
You're always taking me someplace to eat
就像在努力养胖我一样
like you're trying to fatten me up or something.
不 我只是很喜欢
No, I just like the look on your face
当你吃到好吃的时 露出的表情
when something gets real good to you.
那你一定看到过很多次
Mm, you must see that look a lot.
不 还是不一样的
No, it's different, though.
是你的身体 你的笑
It's your body and your smile
你的想法 你思考的方式
and your mind, the way you think.
是你的一切
It's all of you.
无论你变得怎样 都只会是你
It's not what you are. It's who you are.
听着 杰米...
Look, Jamie...
嗯哼 怎么了?
Mmhmm, what?
今晚你愿意过来吗?
Do you want to come over tonight?
那格雷格怎么办?
What about Greg?
再也没有格雷格了
There is no more Greg.
嗯
Hmm.
不要旅馆了 好吗?
No more hotels, okay?
好
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
真是巧啊?
What are the odds?
天啊 汤米
My God, Tommy.
- 你怎么样 安琪 - 还不错
- How you doing, Angie? - Not bad.
- 那你呢? - 看看你
- How about yourself? - Look at you.
我在自力更生 自力更生
I'm holding my own, holding my own.
给我一杯黑白配 大杯
Get me a black-and-white, large.
我刚刚在拜访一个生病的朋友
I was just visiting a sick friend of mine
离这里不远
not too far from here.
他送上了他的问候 然后我就想
He sends his regards, so I figured,
为什么不顺路在回家的路上
why not pick up the best black-and-white
来一杯纽约最好的黑白配呢?
in New York on my way home?
我以为你在夜总会里
I thought you'd be at the club.
你们俩大老远在这做什么呢?
What are you two doing way out here?
噢 你懂的 就是叙叙旧
Oh, you know, just catching up on old times.
感觉真是很久以前了
It seems like forever ago.
我还记得 有一次你想把我介绍给你朋友
I'll never forget the time you tried to hook me up
那火辣的意大利妞
with your friend, the hot one, Italian.
西尔瓦娜 她很喜欢你
Silvana, she had a thing for you.
噢 没有喜欢到允许我上二垒
Oh, not enough to let me get to second base,
相信我 我试过了
and trust me, I tried.
我已经把手伸进去
I got my hand up in there.
她马上就取消了
She cancelled Christmas
和我共度春宵的打算
on your boy with a quickness.
把我直接踢到了街上
Kicked me right out onto the street.
你知道当我们还小的时候
You know who would love these crazy stories
谁最爱听这些故事吗?
about when we was kids?
他老婆 塔莎
His wife, Tasha.
明晚 我们要在夜总会
Tomorrow night, we're having a big birthday party
为她办个生日派对
for her at the club.
你也应该来
You should come.
星期四我得工作到很晚
I work late Thursdays.
噢 真可惜
Aw, too bad.
下次吧
Another time.
我该走了
I'm gonna go.
我可不想你们的雪糕融化了
I don't want your ice creams to melt.
- 谢谢 - 没关系
- Thanks. - You got it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 晚点打给我 - 会的
- Call me later. - You bet.
我还是直接坐列车回城里好了
I think I'm just gonna catch the train back to the city.
安琪 我很抱歉
Angie, I'm sorry.
抱歉什么...抱歉你已经结婚了吗?
Sorry about what... that you're married,
你的好朋友知道你有妻子
that your best friend knows your wife,
他在谈话中随意地提起她
that he mentions her name casually in conversation
就因为他不知道我们的关系吗?
because he doesn't know we're sleeping together?
汤米的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Tommy.
别在意他说的
Forget about everything he said.
听着 我想和在你一起 在这儿
Look, I want to be here with you
晚点在你家
and later at your place.
我会打给你的 杰米
I'll call you, Jamie.
我们有机会 而且我抓住了
We had a shot, and I took it.
不 你让整个行动陷入险境
No, you jeopardized the entire operation on your own.
谁知道以后还有没有
Who knows when or if we would've had
这样的良机?
an opportunity like that?
- 要是这是某人的陷阱呢? - 这不是
- And what if someone made you? - Nobody made me.
- 你确定吗? - 确定
- You're sure about that? - Positive.
因为我知道怎么管好自己
Because I know how to handle myself
场上场下 不像房间中的某个人
on and off the field, unlike some of us in this room.
去你的 麦迪纳
Fuck you, Medina.
我会叫弗兰基给你在缉毒局的上司打电话
I'll have Frankie call your S.A.C. Over at the D.E.A.,
把你送回你来的地方
get you sent back where you came from.
噢 真的吗?
Oh, really?
去吧 去找弗兰基
Vaya. Take it to Frankie.
这样
This way, um,
我才可以公开一些事
I can get a few things out in the open myself.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我尽我所能地阻止他了
I did the best I could to keep him from going in.
他甚至没有看清那个人?
He didn't even get a good look at the guy?
没有
No.
我把音频送到取证处了 看看他们能否处理它
I sent the audio to forensics to see if they can clean it up.
二十四小时内应该会有消息
We should hear something within 24 hours.
嗯好 我就在这
Yeah, well, I'll be here.
杰米来电
已拨通安吉拉・巴尔德斯
Reached Angela Valdes.
我现在没有办法接...
I'm unable to take your...
所以...
So...
昨天午餐很不错嘛 约会剩下的部分怎么样?
Lunch was nice yesterday. How was the rest of the date?
关你屁事
None of your fucking business.
真有趣啊 因为之前的晚上
That's funny, since the other night,
我在见霍莉时 你可是很关心的
you were all up in my business about me seeing Holly.
听着 当你厌烦了这个女孩时...
Look, when you get tired of this girl...
我不会厌烦她
I'm not gonna get tired of her.
好吧 当你真的厌烦了
Okay, well, when you do,
她会很他妈的生气
she's gonna get fucking pissed.
她会搞砸整个夜总会
She's gonna fuck up our whole club,
钱 所有东西 汤米
the money, every fucking thing, Tommy.
你担心我会搞砸夜总会?
You worried about me fucking up the club?
如果塔莎发现了你在勾搭其他女人
If Tasha ever found out that you were nailing another broad,
她会毁了你的家庭 和我们的一切
she'd blow up your family and our whole fucking game.
把你送去警察
She'd take you to the cops
只为让你这偷奸的混蛋烂在监狱里
just to see your cheating ass rot in prison.
第一 你他妈的小声点
First of all, lower your fucking voice, man.
第二 塔莎不会那么做 第三
Secondly, Tasha wouldn't do that, and thirdly,
她永远不会知道 因为你什么都不会说
she ain't gonna know shit 'cause you ain't gonna tell her shit.
噢 还真他妈说对了 我不会告诉她
Oh, you're damn right I ain't gonna tell her.
但这不意味着她不会发现
That don't mean she won't find out.
我赌你的手机里全是安琪的短信
I bet your phone is full of texts from Angie
和动听的语音信息
and cute little voice messages.
"真高兴过了这么久再见到你"
"So good to see you again after all this time"
在我伤了你的心后
after I broke your heart
"还把它扔进了垃圾桶"
"and threw it in a fucking dumpster."
别在意这些 哈?
Forgot all about that, huh?
现在事情不一样了
It's different now.
你结婚了 这就是现在不一样的地方
Yeah, you're married. That's what's different now.
听着 整个事情都在我控制之下
Look, I got the whole situation under control.
是啊
Yeah.
你总认为你把所有东西都控制好了
You always think you got everything on lock.
鲁伊斯说是个女的刺伤了他
Ruiz says a girl stabbed him.
跟袭击莉莉安娜和追赶布埃索的是同一个人
Same as hit Liliana and chased 'Bueso.
鲁伊斯说是个拉丁裔女人 胸很漂亮
Ruiz says it was a Latina chick with nice tits
淡色长发
and long, light-colored hair.
如果我们能问问莉莉安娜
Bet we could get a better description
我们肯定能知道的更多 噢 我的错
if we could ask Liliana, but, whoa, my bad.
我们问不了 因为我们把她冻起来了
We can't, since we had her iced.
不知道我知道这事吧 哈?
Didn't know I knew about that, huh?
我找了那个婊子好几星期
I've been looking at that bitch for weeks,
等着你和我说些什么
waiting for you to say something.
"嘿 汤米 我知道我们决定杀了她"
"Hey, Tommy, I know we agreed to kill her,
但我改变主意了"
but I changed my mind."
说了会有用的
That would've worked.
她活着会更有价值
Thought she was more useful alive.
我做出了决定
I made a judgment call.
现在我们可以让胡里奥回到莉莉安娜那
Now we can have Julio go back to Liliana
看看能不能和鲁伊斯的描述对上
to see if Ruiz's description lines the fuck up,
- 如果她还记得的话 - 是啊
- if she remembers anything. - Yeah.
我们要找到这女的 和她为之工作的人
We gotta find this girl, man, and who she's working for.
这才是有意义的事 汤米
That's all that matter Tommy.
而不是其他那些狗屁
None of this other bullshit.
听着 幽灵
Yo, G.
安吉拉之前是个麻烦
Angela was trouble before,
现在她仍然是
and she's trouble again.
我只是不想看着你被她毁了
I just don't want to see you get fucked up.
就这样
That's all.
嗨 肖恩 我们快好了
Hi, Shawn, we're almost ready.
妈妈 你看上去真漂亮
Mama, you look beautiful.
是啊 这条裙子真漂亮 圣・帕特里克夫人
Yeah, that's a real nice dress, Mrs. St. Patrick.
谢谢你们的夸奖
Thank you both.
雷娜 你看到过我的那对圆形钻石耳环吗?
Raina, have you seen my diamond hoop earrings?
没 我可没笨到动你的的东西
No, I'm smart enough to stay away from your stuff.
但也没聪明到能找到你的那些小饰品
But not smart enough to figure out your fractions.
儿子 作业做完没?
Did you finish your homework, son?
嗯 我就知道
Yeah, that's what I thought.
做完作业再打游戏 好吗?
Game off until you're finished, okay?
- 好了 我们走吧 - 让我先找副耳环
- All right, let's roll out. - Let me find my earrings first.
你瞧着 你妈准会埋怨我
Watch your mama blame me for that somehow.
彼此彼此 老爸
Join the club, dad.
耶
Yeah.
肖恩 你去探望过你父亲了吗?
Shawn, you went to visit your pops?
- 一切还好吗? - 去了 他挺好
- How'd it go? - Yeah, he's good.
不过我觉得他吃的有点少
I don't think he's eating enough, though,
所以他和其他壮男比起来看上去佝偻瘦弱了些
so he's looking a lot leaner and tighter from all the push-ups.
- 带我向他问好了吗? - 当然
- Tell him I sent my regards? - Of course.
他也向你问好
And he sent his back too.
很好
Cool.
肖恩 你能和我爸说说
Can you tell my dad I'm old enough
我已经到了可以看刺客信条的年龄了?
for Assassin's Creed now, Shawn?
你想干啥 想让我被你爸杀死吗?
What you trying to do, get me killed?
去做作业
Do your homework.
- 找到耳环没? - 没有
- Did you find them? - No.
它们早晚会出现的
They'll pop up sooner or later.
快点 我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
好的 你们俩 听外婆的话 好吗
Okay, you two, listen to big mama, all right?
- 好 - 明天早上见
- Okay. - I'll see you in the morning.
晚安 宝贝女儿 看好你妹妹
Good night, baby girl. Take care of your sister.
如果你还想要你的PS3
You want to keep that PS3,
就快去做功课 现在
you do your homework for real, now.
- 晚安 宝贝 - 晚安
- Good night, babies. - Good night.
你准备什么时候才会接我电话?
How long you gonna duck my calls?
除非你对我坦白 否则我们就没什么好说的
Until you're straight with me, there's nothing to talk about.
这就是他妈的钱 你有什么好在意的?
It's just fucking money. Why do you care?
我有钱 我享受
I have it. Enjoy it.
汤米 如果这是你的钱
Tommy, if it was about your money,
我就不会这身打扮 穿这样的鞋和暴露的裙子
I wouldn't be in these heels and this slutty dress.
这时候我已经在家不用辛苦打工
I would be home on my night off.
坎托斯教你这么做的?
Kantos made you come in for this?
我去找那贱人谈谈
Let me talk to that little bitch.
你真不知道我为什么生你的气吗?
Do you really not understand why I'm mad at you?
你生气是因为你不信任我
You're mad because you don't believe me.
但这是你的问题 不是吗? 这和我无关
But that's on you, all right? That's not my problem.
那你为什么还要他妈的打了我一整天的电话
Then why are you fucking calling me all day?
你不能选择
You don't get to pick and choose
让我介入你生活的某个部分
what part of your life you let me into.
听着 霍莉
Look, Holly.
我没骗过你 好吗?
I'm not lying to you, all right?
- 我还有活干 - 霍莉!
- I got work to do. - Holly!
让我们用最热烈的欢呼
We want to give a big shout-out
有请真理酒吧的第一夫人
to the first lady of truth,
塔莎 圣・帕特里克夫人
Mrs. Tasha St. Patrick.
生日快乐 塔莎!
Happy Birthday, Tasha!
好了 我们现在
All right, let's make our way over
- 去VIP 好吗? - 行
- to V.I.P., all right? - Okay.
好的
All right.
特殊招待 我们走
Specl treatment, here we go.
我说一句
Quick thing.
今晚不谈生意
No business tonight.
但这消息你一定想听
But this is the kind of business you want to hear.
西蒙・斯特恩打电话来
Simon Stern called.
相约我们见面
He wants to meet.
明天早上
Tomorrow morning.
生日快乐
Happy Birthday, sis.
- 谢谢你 汤米
- Thank you, Tommy.
本来想像往常一样给你钱的
Rather than give you money, like I always do,
但我觉的这次要用点心思换样东西
figured I'd put some thought into it.
什么?
What?
很不错 汤米
Very nice, Tommy.
你去美容院买的?
You went to the spa to buy this?
当然没有 我有个熟人认识一个人
Hell, no, I know a guy who knows a guy
他刚开了个很棒的分店
that had the hookup to a real fancy joint
那里有桑拿 水流按摩浴缸
with a sauna, jacuzzi.
或许你还能在那做面部护理或者别的什么
Thought maybe you could get a facial or some shit.
你没必要这么做的 汤米
You didn't have to do this, Tommy.
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Thank you. - Yeah, I did.
你这么久以来一直
You supported us for so long,
在背后支持我们
always had our backs.
你值得拥有最好的
You deserve the best.
塔莎 塔莎!
Tasha, Tasha!
- 嗨 - 嘿!
- Hi - Hey!
怎么了?
What?
我只想说
I just want to say
生日快乐 塔什!
Happy Birthday, Tash!
我去去就来
I'll bright back.
噢
Oh.
嘿 塔莎 我正想过来
Hey, Tasha, I was just about to come over
祝你生日快乐
and wish you a Happy Birthday.
你这耳环哪来的?
Where did you get those earrings?
这个?
These?
你他妈的从我家偷的
You stole them from my damn house.
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
别扯淡了
Shut your lying ass up,
如果你还想保住你的饭碗就快点把东西还我
and give me back my shit while you still have a job.
塔莎 这不是你的 是我的东西
Tasha, these aren't yours. They're mine.
汤米买给我的
Tommy bought them for me.
很好 让他亲口告诉我
Good, then he can tell me that himself.
过来
Come on.
- 怎么了? - 请你告诉她...
- What's going on? - Please tell her...
这对耳环是你买给她的?
You buy those earrings for her?
是的 我买的 怎么了 你喜欢?
Yeah, I bought 'em. Why, you like 'em?
我也给你买一副
I would've got you a pair too.
是啊 我很喜欢
Yeah, I do like them.
这对耳环让我想起我以前有过的一副
They remind me of a pair I used to have.
英雄所见略同
Great minds think alike.
过来! 我一个有惊喜给你
Come on! I got a surprise for you.
霍莉!
Holly!
噢 快过来
Oh, just come on.
女士们先生们!
Ladies and gentlemen!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
让我来介绍今晚的女主角
I'd like to introduce the lady of the hour,
塔莎 圣・帕特里克夫人 唱首歌
Mrs. Tasha St. Patrick, to rock the mic.
我他妈的不在自己的生日派对上唱歌
I'm not singing at my own damn birthday party.
为什么不? 碧昂斯就在她生日派对上唱了
Why not? Beyonce did it at hers.
我又不是碧昂斯
I'm not Beyonce.
如果她同意你早就在她团队里了
You would be in her group if she'd let you.
现在 来吧 唱吧
Now, come on. Come on.
# 我还是爱着你 #
I will love you anyway
# 尽管你不会停留 #
even if you cannot stay
# 我相信你就是我的真命天子 #
I think you are the one for me
# 应该在我身边陪伴 #
Here is where you ought to be
# 我只是想让你满意 #
I just want to satisfy you
# 尽管我不能否认你不是我的 #
Though you're not mine I can't deny it
# 你没听到我说的吗 宝贝? #
Don't you hear me talking, baby?
# 现在就爱上我 否则我将疯狂 #
Love me now, or I'll go crazy
# 噢 宝贝 #
Whoa, sweet thing
# 你难道还不明白你是我的一切? #
don't you know you're my everything?
# 噢 宝贝 #
Whoa, sweet thing
# 你难道还不明白你是我的一切? #
don't you know you're my everything?
# 是的 你就是我的一切 #
Yes, u are?
安琪来电
# 我多希望你是我的爱人 #
I wish you were my lover
# 但你隐藏的如此之深 #
But you're so undercover
嘿 我都在想
Hey, I was beginning to think
你的手机是不是坏了
your phone was broken.
不 没坏
No, not broken.
我说过我会再打给你的
I told you I would call you.
是啊 可我等不及
Well, I couldn't wait that long.
你现在在派对上?
You're at the party now?
是啊 但我更想和你在一块
Yeah, but I'd rather be with you.
我觉得你是说
I think you mean that.
你在那和一大群人在一起
You're there with all those people,
而我在这里 一个人
and I'm here, alone.
但我也一个人 安琪
But I'm alone too, Angie.
是的 我是说 这里有很多人
You know, yes, I mean, there's a lot of people here.
他们大部分都应该是我的朋友
Most of them are supposed to be my friends,
但我如果不和你在一起我就很孤单
but I'm alone when I'm not with you.
我能过来看你吗?
Can I come see you?
你得给我些时间 杰米
You need to give me some time, Jamie.
# 你是我热力的源泉 #
You are my heat
# 你是我的火 #
you are my fire
# 噢 耶 #
Oh, yeah
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢各位
Thanks, everybody.
为塔莎欢呼吧!
Give it up for Tasha!
昨晚派对很棒
Great party last night.
你累吗?
How tired are you?
我不累 我准备好了
I'm not. I'm ready.
先生们 欢迎
Gentlemen, welcome.
感谢你们拨冗光临
Thank you for venturing up here.
这是我们的荣幸
Pleasure, sir.
啊 神秘的詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
Ah, the elusive James St. Patrick.
西蒙・斯特恩 认识你们很高兴
Simon Stern. Pleasure.
请进 你们随意
Come in. Make yourself comfortable.
来 请坐
Here, have a seat.
让我直奔主题
Let me cut to the chase.
辛西娅・谢里丹把她一票交给我做的生意
Cynthia Sheridan took her business from me
交给了你和你的俱乐部
to come to you and your club...
- 真理酒吧 - 真理
- Truth. - Truth.
这给我带来了大麻烦
That vexed me a great deal.
- 这不是针对你个人的 - 当然不是
- It wasn't personal, sir. - Of course not.
但这会让我觉得要么你傻
But it made me think either you're stupid
并且不在乎利益...
and don't care about profit...
因为这么大的生意
because you basically gave
你几乎是白送啊
the whole cow away for free...
要不你很精明 具备我所没有的东西
or you're smart and have something I don't.
除了辛西娅・谢里丹的派对?
Other than the Cynthia Sheridan parties?
我们每晚都能挣个满钵
We have a full house every night,
还有五百人在寒风中等着进来
another 500 waiting out in the cold,
我们预聘了两个DJ 还有个名人专用入口
two DJs on retainer, a back entrance for celebrities.
我有种预感西蒙已经知道我们的数据了
Something tells me Simon knows our stats already.
你是想问我们凭什么能
You're asking what makes us more than just lightning
做大做强
in a bottle.
你说的对 我就这个意思
You're right, I am.
你想知道我要提供给你什么
You're wanting to know what I have to offer you.
你要给我个展示的机会
Well, you have to make me an offer.
我明白了
I see.
霍莉! 霍霍
Holly! Hoy.
唷 霍莉! 我正到处找你呢
Yo, Holly! Been looking all over for you.
- 快上车 - 滚你的
- Get in the car. - Fuck you.
你偷了塔莎的东西 而我撒谎帮你掩饰
You stole from Tasha, and I lied to cover your ass.
现在快他妈上车!
Now get in the fucking car!
你算哪门子罪犯?
What kind of fucking criminal are you?
你欠我一个人情
You owe me one now.
拜托 上车吧
Come on, get in the car.
你他妈脑子里想的什么玩意
What the fuck you thinking
偷塔莎 我的家人的东西?
stealing from Tasha, my family?
我不觉得她会想念它们
I didn't think she would miss them.
她的衣柜就像一个百货商店
Her closet, it's like a fucking department store.
她到底有多少东西都没关系
It doesn't matter how much shit she has.
她就像我姐姐一样
She's like my sister.
在我们去之前我就告诉过你了
I told you that before we went to their place.
听着...
Look...
我喜欢顺手牵羊
I like to take shit.
我这人就是这样
That's just who I am.
但我很抱歉 我知道这是个混账事
I'm sorry, though. It was a dick move.
你要想的话可以向她告发我
You can rat me out to her if you want.
等会 你想去哪?
Whoa, where you going now?
我在你家发现的那些钱 汤米...
All that money I found in your place, Tommy...
那不是俱乐部里来的吧
that's not from the club.
不 不是
No, it's not.
但是如果你要当我的女朋友的话
But if you're gonna be my girl,
我要能相信你 霍莉
I gotta be able to trust you, Holly.
我告诉你的事
What I tell you,
你...你不能告诉任何人
you... Can't tell nobody
因为没有别的人知道
'cause nobody else knows.
我想知道
I want to know.
事情就是
Thing is,
我偷偷在卖一些毒品来赚外快
I sell some dope on the side to make a little extra money.
我是个毒贩
I'm a drug dealer.
我他妈的不蠢
I'm not fucking stupid.
可你的电话又没有一天到晚都在响
Your phone isn't ringing day and night.
你也没住破烂窝
You don't live in some shitty wackup.
而且仅靠一点毒品的收入是开不得起夜店的
And there's no way "some dope" pays for a nightclub.
不管你在做什么 都不仅仅是爱好了
Whatever you're doing ain't a goddamn hobby.
告诉我真相 汤米
Tell me the truth, Tommy.
我处在这个食物链的顶层
I'm at the top of the food chain.
我有一堆混混帮我跑腿
I got a crew of motherfuckers hustling for me,
而且我们已经把生意做大了
and we move serious weight.
如果我想脱身 我就要被灭口
If I go away, I go away for good.
你想要真相
You wanted the truth.
是 没错
Yeah, I did.
那么你怎么看的?
So what you think?
我是个混账小偷
I am a fucked-up thief,
你是个疯子毒贩
and you are a crazy drug dealer.
我认为
I think
我们俩命中注定 天造地设
you and I were made for each other.
你来了
You're here.
我来了
I'm here.
没提前告诉我
Unannounced.
我喜欢来点惊喜
I like the element of surprise.
你说你和格雷格已经分手了
You said you and Greg are over.
我们分了
We are.
所以我能进来吗?
So can I come in?
我觉得这不是个好主意
I think that's a bad idea.
我今天去见西蒙・斯特恩了
I saw Simon Stern today.
进展很顺利
It went great.
他想共进晚餐 还一直在讲未来的发展
He wants to have dinner, keep talking about a future.
恭喜你 杰米
Congratulations, Jamie.
我真为你高兴
I'm really happy for you.
我第一个就想告诉你
You're the first person I wanted to tell.
实际上 我只想告诉你
In fact, you're the only person I wanted to tell.
当我和你在一起时
When I'm with you,
我控制不住自己
I can't hold myself back.
我想要控制
I want to.
我想要在乎现实情况
I want the reality to matter,
但我做不到
but it doesn't.
我的眼里只有你
I just see you.
没你在身边我觉得我整个人都不对
I get wrong when I'm away from you.
我需要另一记重击才能走上正轨
I need another hit to get right.
另一记重击?
Another hit?
就是这种感觉
That's exactly how it feels.
我恨不得把你整个人吞了
我正努力克制自己不要见你
I was so committed to not seeing you,
而你就敲响我家的门
and then you just knock on my door,
我让你进来了
and I let you in.
女孩就只有这点决心
A girl only has so much resolve.
对不起
Sorry.
不 你没做错什么
No, you're not.
你到底想说些什么?
What were you even supposed to talk about anyway?
斯特恩
Stern.
我的会议
My meeting.
告诉我
Tell me.
说吧
Come on.
我不想操之过急
Well, I don't want to get ahead of myself,
但我们聊了合伙
but we talked about partnering,
扩展
expansion,
维加斯 迈阿密
Vegas, Miami.
我喜欢迈阿密
Mm, I like Miami.
抱歉 宝贝
Sorry, babe.
我明白
I know.
我不想让你走
I don't want you to go.
我也不想走
I don't want to go.
我想 就没有别的办法...
I mean, is there any way...
你今晚能留下来吗?
could you stay the night?
当我没问 我知道你的回答
Never mind, I know the answer.
现实所迫
Reality calls.
我也希望我能 安琪
I wish I could, Angie.
嘿 过来
Hey, hey.
不会一直这样的
It won't always be like this.
嗯 好吧
Yeah, okay.
我保证
I promise.
真的谢谢你 肖恩
Thank you so much, Shawn.
我希望你有享受
I hope you got a chance to enjoy
那晚的派对
some of the party the other night.
没错 我玩的开心
Yeah, I did.
实际上
Actually, um...
我给你带了点东西
I got you a little something myself.
肖恩 你没必要这么客气
Shawn, you did not have to do that.
你已经做的够多了
You do enough already.
没事 只是点小心意
Nah, it's just a little something.
我希望这能让你开心
I hope it makes you smile.
我听说你丢了一对耳环 所以 嗯...
I heard you say you lost a pair of earrings, so, um...
耳环真美
They're beautiful.
但我不能收下
But I can't accept them.
我不想幽灵误会
I wouldn't want Ghost to get the wrong idea.
好吧
Yeah.
好吧 就这样
Yeah, right.
不好意思?
Excuse me?
你说什么?
What was that?
肖恩 你刚刚说什么?
Shawn, what did you just say?
没什么 我什么都没说
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
我的意思是
I mean,
你值得一个像你对他一样对你忠诚的人
you deserve someone who's as loyal to you as you are to him.
你这是什么意思?
What the hell does that mean?
他总是看重其他的事多过你
He's always just putting other stuff ahead of you.
但我又知道什么?
But what the hell do I know?
我只是个司机 是吧?
I'm just the driver, right?
我要所有人在车库
I need men down in the garage
和门那里戒备好
and at all the doors.
有人来了
Someone coming.
安保要严
Security needs to be tight.
谁知道那个混球计划了些什么
Who knows what this fucking asshole has planned.
谁?
Who?
我希望是幽灵
I'm expecting Ghost,
那个给我们提供货
the pendejo who supplies us
但也最有可能杀了我的蠢货
and most likely put these fucking holes in me.
这个该死的
What this fucking
都策划了些什么
fucking asshole has planned.
谁?
Who?
我希望是幽灵
I'm expecting Ghost,
那个给我们提供货
the pendejo who supplies us
但也最有可能杀了我的蠢货
and most likely put these fucking holes in me.
- 你想我去搜他的身? - 你想怎样?
- You want me to frisk him? - What do you think?
我告诉你 这个混账
I'm telling you this piece of shit
想杀了我 而你问我
tried to have me killed, and you're asking me
你是否看到他携带枪支?
if you should see if he's carrying a weapon?
这个该死的
What the fuck?
- 都策划了些什么
- [Speaking spanish] Has planned.
谁?
Who?
我希望是幽灵
I'm expecting Ghost,
那个给我们提供货源
the pendejo who supplies us
但又最有可能杀了我的蠢货
and most likely put these fucking holes in me.
你想我去搜他的身?
You want me to frisk him?
我希望是幽灵
I'm expecting Ghost.